<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Agustin Mautone on agusit</title>
    <link>http://agusit7.github.io/authors/agustin-mautone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Agustin Mautone on agusit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:44:11 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://agusit7.github.io/authors/agustin-mautone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Improving the diversity of generative models using evolutive computing</title>
      <link>http://agusit7.github.io/posts/research-thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:44:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://agusit7.github.io/posts/research-thesis/</guid>
      <description>This article presents a multiobjective evolutionary approach for coevolutionary training of Generative Adversarial Networks. The proposal applies an explicit multiobjective optimization approach based on Pareto ranking and non-dominated sorting over the co-evolutionary search implemented by the Lipizzaner framework, to optimize the quality and diversity of the generated synthetic data. Two functions are studied for evaluating diversity. The main results obtained for the handwritten digits generation problem show that the proposed multiobjective search is able to compute accurate and diverse solutions, improving over the standard Lipizzaner implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLconf 2020 session: AI for the conservation of the African lion</title>
      <link>http://agusit7.github.io/posts/lion-ai-tak/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 23:44:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://agusit7.github.io/posts/lion-ai-tak/</guid>
      <description>Video recording Link to heading LINC website Link to heading About the session Link to heading Panthera leo (the African lion) is now an endangered species. Over the last 20 years approximately 42% of its habitat has been lost, creating fragmented populations across the African continent. The accurate monitoring of lion populations and a better understanding of the connectivity between them is critical to maintaining the genetic viability of these increasingly isolated populations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
